Guide to the Yale School of Music Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Music student records
1905-2013
RU 265
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
101.5
(141 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the Office of the Registrar at the Yale School of Music.
Yale School of Music
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 28-F (YRG 28-F), Student records of the Yale School of Music.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the Office of the Registrar at the Yale School of Music.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Yale School of Music; Yale University -- Students
- Student records, 1909-1976; Accession 1983-A-028
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052.
  - Student Records, 1909-1976
    - 1909-1939
    - A - Sup, 1909-1939 (Box 1)
    - Sug - Z, 1909-1939 (Box 2)
    - 1940-1976
    - A - Arc, 1940-1976 (Box 3)
    - Ard - Bat, 1940-1976 (Box 4)
    - Bau - Blai, 1940-1976 (Box 5)
    - Blaj - Broo, 1940-1976 (Box 6)
    - Brop - Carr, 1940-1976 (Box 7)
    - Carroll - Cohen, C., 1940-1976 (Box 8)
    - Cohen, D. - Cs, 1940-1976 (Box 9)
    - Dic - Ei, 1940-1976 (Box 11)
    - Fj - Feld, 1940-1976 (Box 12)
    - Fele - Fz, 1940-1976 (Box 13)
    - Ga - Gof, 1940-1976 (Box 14)
    - Gog - Gro, 1940-1976 (Box 15)
    - Gru - Har, 1940-1976 (Box 16)
    - Has - Hold, 1940-1976 (Box 17)
    - Hole - Jab, 1940-1976 (Box 18)
    - Jac - Jou, 1940-1976 (Box 19)
    - Kin - Land, 1940-1976 (Box 21)
    - Lane - Lig, 1940-1976 (Box 22)
    - Lih - McDonald, J., 1940-1976 (Box 23)
    - McDonald, K - Mason, 1940-1976 (Box 24)
    - Masop - Monr, 1940-1976 (Box 25)
    - Mons - Noo, 1940-1976 (Box 26)
    - Nop - Pari, 1940-1976 (Box 27)
    - Parj - Polia, 1940-1976 (Box 28)
    - Polib - Reid, 1940-1976 (Box 29)
    - Reie - Robe, 1940-1976 (Box 30)
    - Robf - Russe, 1940-1976 (Box 31)
    - Russf - Sei, 1940-1976 (Box 32)
    - Sej - Simpson, E., 1940-1976 (Box 33)
    - Simpson, F. - Spir, 1940-1976 (Box 34)
    - Spis - Sullivan, J., 1940-1976 (Box 35)
    - Sullivan, K. - Th, 1940-1976 (Box 36)
    - Ti - Van, 1940-1976 (Box 37)
    - Vao - Weinf, 1940-1976 (Box 38)
    - Weing - Wis, 1940-1976 (Box 39)
    - Wit - Z, 1940-1976 (Box 40)
  - Student Records: Background Cards
    - A - Z, 1919-1939 (Box 41)
  - Non-Student Records: Background Cards
    - A - Colen, 1940-1976 (Box 42)
    - Coleo - Gz, 1940-1976 (Box 43)
    - H - Lore, 1940-1976 (Box 44)
    - Lorf - Q, 1940-1976 (Box 45)
    - R - T, 1940-1976 (Box 46)
    - U - Z, 1940-1976 (Box 47)
- Student transcripts (microfilm), 1909-2002; Accession 1983-A-029
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - A-Z; A-D, 1909-Circa 1976 (Reel 1)
  - D-K, 1940-1976? (Reel 2)
  - K-P, 1940-1976? (Reel 3)
  - P-S, 1940-1976? (Reel 4)
  - S-Z, 1940-1976? (Reel 5)
  - A-Z, 1977-1982 (Reel 6)
  - Graduates-Appendix [left out of original run], 1952-1981 (Reel 7)
  - Separate partials [ex-students], 1976-1981 (Reel 8)
  - Graduates 1982 and partials, 1978-1982 (Reel 9)
  - Graduates 1983 and partials, 1979-1983 (Reel 10)
  - Graduates 1984; partials 1983 and 1984, 1979-1984 (Reel 11)
  - Graduates 1985; partials 1983-1984, 1979-1985 (Reel 12)
  - 1985-1986; partials for 1983-1986, 1979-1986 (Reel 13)
  - 1987 (Reel 14)
  - 1988 (Reel 15)
  - 1989 (Reel 16)
  - 1990 (Reel 17)
  - 1991 (Reel 18)
  - 1992 (Reel 19)
  - 1993 (Reel 20)
  - 1994 (Reel 21)
  - 1995 (Reel 22)
  - 1996 (Reel 23)
  - 1997 (Reel 24)
  - 1998 (Reel 25)
  - 1999 (Reel 26)
  - 2000 (Reel 27)
  - 2001 (Reel 28)
  - 2002 (Reel 29)
- Student transcripts (microfilm), Accession 1994-A-093
- Student records for the Classes of 1977-1979, 1973-1979; Accession 1985-A-011
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  - Class of 1977
  - Class of 1978
  - Class of 1979
- Student records for the Class of 1980, 1976-1980; Accession 1986-A-102
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
- Student records for the Class of 1981, 1977-1981; Accession 1988-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
- Student records for the Class of 1982, 1978-1982; Accession 1989-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
- Student records for the Class of 1983, 1979-1983; Accession 1990-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Certificate in Performance
  - Master of Music
  - Master of Musical Arts
  - Doctor of Musical Arts
  - Partial Transcripts
- Student records for the Classes of 1984-1994, Accession 2001-A-016
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - 1984
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - Partial transcripts
  - 1985
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - Partial transcripts
  - 1986
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - PARTIALS
  - 1983
  - 1984
  - 1985
  - 1986
  - 1987
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - 1988
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - 1989
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - PARTIALS
  - CONVERSION FROM CERTIFICATE TO MM
  - 1990
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - LEAVE OF ABSENCE
  - 1991
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 503)
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - OTHERS NO DATES ON TRANSCRIPTS
  - 1992
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - ARTIST DIPLOMA
  - LEAVE OF ABSENCE/DROP OUTS
  - 1993
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - ARTIST DIPLOMA
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
  - CERTIFICATE OF PERFORMANCE
  - LEAVE OF ABSENCE/DROP OUTS
  - 1994
  - ARTIST DIPLOMA
  - MASTER OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - DOCTOR OF MUSICAL ARTS
  - WITHDRAWALS
  - STUDENTS WHO CONVERTED THEIR CERT. TO A MM
  - CERTIFICATE IN PERFORMANCE
  - MASTER OF MUSIC
- Student records for the Class of 1995, Accession 2001-A-165
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
- Student records for the Classes of 1985-1994, Accession 2001-A-166
  - 1985
  - 1986
  - 1987
  - 1988
  - 1989
  - 1990
  - 1991
  - 1992
  - 1993
  - 1994
- Student records for the Class of 1996, Accession 2003-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
- Student records for the Class of 1997, Accession 2003-A-152
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
- Student records for the Class of 1998, Accession 2004-A-192
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
- Student grades, 1996-2000; Accession 2004-A-197
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - Fall 1996 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1997 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1997 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1998 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1998 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1999 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1999 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2000 (Box 1)
- Student records for the Class of 1999, Accession 2005-A-176
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
- Student records for the Class of 2000, Accession 2007-A-004
- Student records for the Class of 2001, Accession 2008-A-019
- Student records for the Class of 2002, 2000-2002; Accession 2008-A-177
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078.
- Student records for the Class of 2003, 2001-2003; Accession 2009-A-197
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2079
- Student records for the Class of 2004, 2002-2004; Accession 2011-A-002
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2080
- Student records for the Class of 2005, Accession 2013-A-032
  Restricted until January 1, 2080.
- Student records for the Class of 2006, Accession 2014-A-036
  Restricted until January 1, 2081.
- Student records for the Class of 2007, 2003-2007; Accession 2014-A-047
  Restricted until January 1, 2082.
- Student records for the Class of 2008, 2005-2008; Accession 2014-A-072
  Restricted until January 1, 2083.
- Student records for the Class of 2009, 2004-2009; Accession 2015-A-046
  Restricted until January 1, 2084.
- Student records for the Class of 2010, 2006-2010; Accession 2016-A-036
  Restricted until January 1, 2086.
  - (Conferred to MM 6/9/04), 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Student records for the Class of 2011, 2007-2011; Accession 2017-A-005
  Restricted until January 1, 2087.
- Student records for the Class of 2012, 2008-2012; Accession 2018-A-004
  Restricted until January 1, 2088.
- Student records for the Class of 2013, 2009-2013; Accession 2018-A-080
  Restricted until January 1, 2089
  - Affleck (McPhail), Catherine, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen, John Stewart, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Gregory N., 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bak, Brian Giho, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ban, Sun Kyung, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Beloglavec, Hana, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bennetch, Caleb, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bortolameolli, Paolo, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Buide, Fernando, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Buzard, Stephen Michael, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Caccese, Victor, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chang, Heejin, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chang Hen-Shuo (Steven), 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chartrand, Megan Yvonne, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cheung, Alissa, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cheung, Wai Ching Rachel, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chiang, Leonard Tung, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Choi, Arnold Albert, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Choi, Go Woon, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Choi, Minhye Helena, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ehrenburg, John Matthew, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Feigenbaum, Stephen, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Fournelle-Blain, Victor, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Gajardo-Benitez, Cristobal, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Guo, Yue (Grace), 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Hahn, Alexander, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Hayhurst, Andrew, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Hilgert, Timothy, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Hill, Kelly Anne, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hunt, Lauren, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - James, Eleanor Kendra, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Jancaitis, Holland J., 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Jung, Wonyoung, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Kanasevich, Hleb, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Kang, Cho-Long, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Katayama, Yuki Heidi, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Kim, Eun Taek, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Kim, Eunchan, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Kim, Jeonghwan, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    General
    Converted to MM August 2, 2-16
  - Kim, Ji Hyun (James), 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Kim, Ji hyun, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Kim, Joonwhan, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Kim, Nayeon, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Kim, Shinae (Jeannie), 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Lee, Corin (Cory), 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Lee, Seok Jung, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Levin, Igal, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Li, Jessica (Jess), 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Liu, Jian, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Liu, Qizhen, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Ma, Yuan, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Mata, Gerardo Garcia (Gerry), 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - McWilliams, Jonathan, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Mello, Scott Joseph, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Milholin, Nathan, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Milovanov, Alexander, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Mitchell, Jane, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Moffett, Kayla, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Moore, Shawn, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Naylor Bradley MacNaughton, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Nazaykinskaya, Polina Sergeevna, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Nesbitt, Dashiel (Dash), 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Park, Jennifer Jinhee, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Paw, Cordelia, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Perry, David Treston, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Petrucci, Ginevra, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Quah, Melody, 2009-2013 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Reinhardt, Jeffrey, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Richard-Hamelin, Charles, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Rosenthal, Matthew Haupt, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ross, Caroline Woods, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rossi, Sara Elizabeth, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ruiz, Hermelindo, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Salas, Galeano, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Salazar, Michael Theodore, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Schaeffer, Andrew, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Seung, Kyeong Hoon, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Shin, Hae Yoon, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Shotwell, Vivien, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Siladie, Jenna, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sitzmann, Christian, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Small, Andrew, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Song, NaHee, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Song, Yoon Won, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Soph, Steven, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Steele, Dana, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Strebendt, Robert, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Tam, Adrianna Lynn, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - teVelde, Brent Arthur, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Thomas, Paul Braxton, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Tomesch, Ian, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - van der Zanden, Jurrian Henderik, 2009-2013 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Villella, Gerald Joseph, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Warnken, Virginia Anne, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Weber, Amanda, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Woo, Naomi Meghan, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Yanagitani, Ryosuke, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Yang, Jiin, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Yu, Lauren, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Zhang, Bo, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Zhang, Dan, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 9)